Mohamed Ahmed Basyoni

Multimedia

 \boxtimes

basyonifilmmaker@gmail.com



+966506843710

9

Riyadh - Saudi Arabia

Objective

Highly imaginative filmmaker with a solid seven years of experience making a variety of films for a variety of industries. Have a strong passion for creating independent films, but also have a knack for creating commercials, commercial productions, documentaries, and short films utilizing my knowledge of the latest camera, video, and audio equipment and editing software.

Experience

Per4Max Agency	JUN 2024 - Present
Creative Art Director Filmmaker	
 opacity-adv 	JUN 2023 - JUN 2024
Video editing and Filmmaker	
 Vision Co. of Saudi Arabia 	JUN 2022 - JUN 2023
Video editing and Videographer	
 Wasila Academy for Media Production 	Nov 2019 - Jun 2021
Founder, Cairo	
Next Video Production	Oct 2019 - Aug 2018
Videographer, Cairo	
 Freelance videographer and editor 	Oct 2018 - Aug 2016
Videographer, Cairo	

Education

Faculty Of Business - Ain Shams University	
Egypt, Ain Shams	2021

Certifications

Oct 2022
JUL 2021
NOV 2020
Sep 2019
Sep 2018
Apr 2017

Personal details

LinkedIn

<u>linkedin.com/in/basyonifilmmaker</u> website

https://mohamed-basyoni.github.io/

Skills

Technical skills:

- ADOBE PREMIERE
- ADOBE AFTER EFFECTS
- ADOBE AUDITION
- ADOBE PHOTOSHOP
- DAVINCI RESOLVE
- ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR
- ADOBE LIGHTROOM
- RONIN STABILIZERS
- CAMERAS (SONY-CANON-NIKON)

Interpersonal skills:

- Very good oral and written communication skills.
- Ability to work independently, as well as within a team of multidisciplinary professionals.
- Analytical and critical thinking skills.
- Ability to work with sophisticated technology.

Languages:

• Arabic: native

• English: B1

References

References are available upon request.